[Music]
oh
girl i'm in love with you
but this ain't a honeymoon
we're past the infatuation face
right in the thick of love
at times we get sick of love
it seems like we argue every day
i know i
misbehave and you made your mistake and
we both still got room left to roll
and though love sometimes hurt i still
put you first and we'll make this thing
work but i think we should take it slow
we're just ordinary people
we don't know which way to go
[Music]
this time we'll take it
this ain't the movie no no fairy tales
conclusion y'all
it gets more confusion every day
oh
sometimes it happens and then we head
back to hell again
we kiss them we make up on the way
i hang up you call we rise and we fall
and we feel like just walking away
as our love advances we take second
chances though it's not a fan to see i
still want you to stay we're just
ordinary people
[Music]
we don't know which way to go
cause we aren't in any people
maybe
[Music]
this time we'll take it slow
take it slow
[Music]
maybe we'll
crash maybe you'll stay maybe you'll
leave maybe you'll retire
maybe another fight
maybe we won't survive maybe we'll grow
we'll never know baby
[Music]
we don't know which way to go
yeah
cause we are
[Music]
we don't know which way to
maybe we should take it
take it slow
[Music]
this time we'll take kids
you